Now listen, yo!
People put your guns up
Mazu ore ga run dat
Hashirimawatte yatsura o gun shot
Brand new sound sou still survival
Here come the sound boy kono sekai ni ikiro
Chiryoku tairyoku to un ga mau ze! Flow
Fukuranda ataman naka wa zakkubaran nan da
Savannah de Banna ni wanpan
Kantan knockout kan kan kan
One time for your mind ikinuke
Around the world
Tsukimatou no sa itsu no itami mo
Kedakai kami no mawari mo ima karimono
Makareta tane mo hana sakeba dare no
Ikite uchikomu shinnen no ya o more more more
Ikisaki ni yasuragi wa nai
Tachi na sa don't give up the fight
Ima sou kono shunkan mo die die die
Big shooter ikiisoide blazing
Beat you up kirihiraite break
Shot shooter ikiisoida crazy
Shoujun au shikin kyori de break
Big shooter ikiisoide blazing
Beat you up kirihiraite break
Shot shooter ikiisoida crazy
Shoujun au shikin kyori de break
（計(けい)）これ や… やべえかも
This could be really bad...
（亮太(りょうた)）
おばあちゃん どこ行くの？
Grandma, where are we going?
Home.
（カヨ）
帰るんだよ お母さんの所に
I'm taking you back to your mother.
Yeah, this is really bad...
（計）やっぱ やべえって
（岸本(きしもと)）玄野(くろの)君…
Kurono...
I'm getting used to this.
（計）ちょっと平気になってる
吐き気とかしねえし
I don't feel nauseated anymore...
人死ぬの―
I'm not even... scared or feel sorry
when I see people die...
あんまり 怖いとか かわいそうとか
思わなくなってきてる
Huh? Did you just say something?
（計）あっ… 何か言った？
What's the matter?
どうしたの？
（計）な… 何でも…
Oh, nothing...
This is Japan, right? And we're in the
middle of a residential area...
（計）
ここ… 日本の それも住宅街だよな
（計）俺 なんで
戦争みたいなことしてんだ？
So why do I feel like I'm in a war?
（計）こんな物(もん)持って…
なんでなんだよ？
What am I doing with this thing anyway?
All I know is that I better
make sure to hold on to it...
だけど とにかく
こいつだけは持ってないと…
やべえよな やっぱ
If I don't it's gonna be bad...
Kato, You Wait Here
What are we supposed to do?
（鉄男(てつお)）どうすんだよ？
There's more of 'em, right?
（北条(ほうじょう)）まだ いるんだろう？
（加藤(かとう)）ああ
Yeah...
計ちゃん あのばあさんと子供は？
Kei, where'd the old lady and the kid go?
（計）えっ？
（岸本）いない…
Uh...
They're gone.
（加藤）マズイ
Crap...
Those two are screwed if they
run into the other alien.
（北条）残りのヤツと出くわしたら
まあ アウトだろうな あの２人じゃ
（春哉(はるや)）おい なに寝ぼけてんだ？
あんなばばあと―
Hey, snap out of it!
Why the hell we should we care about the
old bag and that annoying little shit anyway?
ピーピーうるせえガキなんか
放っとけ！
（鉄男）春哉！ ガキってのは
うるさくて当たり前なんだよ！
Haruya! Kids are supposed to be like that!
Why don't you shut the hell up?
うるせえ！ てめえは黙ってろ！
いつまでリーダーづらしてんだよ？
How long are you gonna keep acting
like you're the goddamn leader?
Kosuke and Kinji...
康介(こうすけ)と欣二(きんじ)はな
頭 吹っ飛ばされたんだぞ
They both got their heads blown off!
てめえなんか
何もできなかったじゃねえかよ
And you couldn't do shit!
あいつら
助けられなかったじゃねえかよ！
You couldn't even save them!
So who the hell do you think you are?
ああ？ こら！
It's just like with the guns...
I guess even puking has a time-lag...
（計）この銃みてえ
ゲロ吐くのにもタイムラグあんだ？
Kurono! What are you saying?!
玄野君 何言ってるの？
Well, you sure are walking tall now,
aren't you, Haruya?
（鉄男）
言いたい放題だな 春哉 ああ？
当たり前だ！
文句あんなら俺の歯ぁ返せよ 歯！
You're damn right!
If you don't like it why don't ya
give me my tooth back! How about that?
You son of a bitch...
（鉄男）てめえ…
（加藤）自由になりたいヤツは
俺の言うことを聞け！
Listen to me if you wanna
be free from this!
I'm going to go find
the other Suzuki Alien!
（加藤）これから俺は
もう１匹の鈴木(すずき)星人を捕まえに行く
And I'll see if I can find the
old lady and the boy while I'm at it.
途中で ばあさんたちも
捜し出さないとなんねえ
本当に生き残りたいヤツは
俺に協力してくれ！
If you really want to survive,
then please help me out!
You said something earlier
about getting free from this...
（北条）さっき 言ってたよな
自由になる方法とか
点数が どうしたとか…
Something about a
score or whatever, right?
（加藤）
俺にも本当かどうかは分からない
I don't even know if it's true or not,
but we'll never find out unless we try.
でも やってみるしか…
それしか今はない
At this point, it's the only choice we have!
（北条）はっきり言って
お前を信じて命を預ける気はない
To be honest with you, I don't
feel like trusting you with my life.
でも あのゾク 何もしてないのに
頭飛んで死んだんだろう？
But that biker guy... He got his
head blown away for no reason, right?
Where did it happen?
（加藤）どの辺りだ？
この先 ちょっと行って
角曲がった辺りの電話ボックスの前
If you head straight down this way,
there's a payphone right around the corner.
Right in front of the phone booth.
The bastards...
くそが！
（加藤）多分
このエリアから出ると殺されるんだ
Sounds like you'll die
if you go out of this area.
１キロ四方くらいか
It's about 1 square kilometer...
Do you think there's like a bomb or
something planted in each of our heads?
もしかして 全員 頭ん中に―
何か爆弾みたいなの
入ってるのかな？
Who's keeping us in this area
and for what reason?
誰が何のために閉じ込めてんだ？
（春哉）意味分かんねえってんだよ
This shit doesn't make any sense!
I don't know who's doing this to us either.
（加藤）俺だって
誰が やらせてんのか知らない
The time limit is one hour...
タイムリミットが１時間
And we have to find two of those monsters
within a 1 square kilometer block?
１キロ四方内で
あのバケモノを２匹捕まえるだと？
Well, we did it last time.
前回は やった
でも 毎回できるとは限らない
But that doesn't mean
we can do that every time.
こいつは そんな中を
何度も生き延びてきたことになる
So that means he'd survived
many rounds up to now.
（春哉）フン！ こんなガキが？
A little brat like him?
（鉄男）
こいつが康介 やったんだぜ
He killed Kosuke, remember?
Listen, the fact is we have to
find that other alien!
（加藤）とにかく
もう１匹捕まえるしかないんだ
If you don't believe that,
you can do whatever you want.
信じないヤツは勝手にしてくれ
（加藤）計ちゃんはスーツ着てない
今回は安全な所にいてくれ
Kei, you aren't wearing a suit.
So this time I want you to
stay somewhere safe.
Hey, what happened?
（計）
あのな… さっき 俺のこと―
Just a minute ago you were looking at me like
you thought I was actually cool or something.
ちょっとカッコよさげに
見てたじゃねえかよ
何なんだよ？
What's your problem?
For the meantime,
you walk the way I tell you to.
とりあえず
お前 俺の言うとおり歩け
Huh?!
はぁ？
（春哉）“はぁ”じゃねえだろう！
You heard me!
Hey, Haruya!
おい 春哉！
（春哉）てめえもだよ
You, too, asshole!
Frickin' has-been "leader"!
リーダー崩れのダサダサ野郎
それ よこせよ
Give me that thing.
いってえ… あっ…
Damn, that hurt...
Hurry up and hand it over!
（春哉）早くしろ ほら！
（鉄男）春哉 てめえ…
Haruya, you son of a...
Hey, you!
（春哉）こら てめえ！
コソコソ逃げんじゃねえよ
戻ってこい！
You ain't sneaking off on me!
Get back over here!
Where...
（加藤）どこだ？ どこにいる？
Where?
Who do you mean? The old lady,
or the Suzuki Alien?
（北条）
ばあさんか？ 鈴木星人か？
Both.
（加藤）どっちもだ
Why don't we ask this taxi for help?
（北条）
あの運ちゃんに助けてもらったら？
（加藤）ダメなんだ
It won't work.
終わるまで
俺たちの姿は誰にも見えないらしい
It looks like we're invisible to
everyone else until this thing is over.
So does this mean we really are dead?
それ ホントに死んだってことか？
I wonder where we are...
どこなのかしら？ ここ
I'm hungry! I can't walk anymore!
（亮太）
おなかすいた　もう歩けない～…
（カヨ）ハァ… 困ったねえ
Oh dear...
Who the fuck told you to stop?
（春哉）タコ 止まるんじゃねえよ
いってえな…
Ow...
Are you crying? Pathetic!
泣いてやんの　情けねえ
Son of a bitch...
（計）ちくしょう…
Now walk! C'mon, hurry up!
（春哉）歩け オラ 早く！
Hey, Kato...
（岸本）ねえ 加藤君
（加藤）うん？
You're not going to use guns?
（岸本）銃 撃たないの？
It might be better if you do, though...
撃ったほうがいいんじゃないかな？
（加藤）えっ？
I mean...
えっと… 加藤君
一生懸命やってくれてると思う
I think you're trying really hard.
でも その…
But... Well...
お前が もっと早く撃ってれば
あの中坊は もしかしたら…
If you'd pulled the trigger
a little sooner,
that kid might have been all right.
（岸本）そ… そこまでは
言ってないつもりなんだけど…
That's not what I was trying to say!
女ってさ
生存本能ってやつ強いんだ？
Women usually have stronger
survival instincts...
そうは思わないけど
Well, I don't think that's true!
No. You... you're right.
（加藤）そ… そうだな
（岸本）加藤君…
Kato...
撃たないとダメだよな
I should be ready to shoot.
（北条）近い… 近いはずだ
It's close...
It should be nearby.
But which is it?
どっち？ 鈴木星人？
それとも おばあちゃんたち？
The Suzuki Alien or
the old lady and the kid?
I can't tell.
（北条）これだけじゃ分からない
No, we don't know...
but we will in a minute!
誰だか分かんねえけど来るぞ
（北条・岸本）あっ…
Hurry the fuck up!
You still haven't figured it out?!
（春哉）
早くしろ まだ分かんねえのか？
This is not mine, so it
looks like it works differently.
（計）俺んじゃないから
使い方 違うみたいなんだよ
（鉄男）自分のなら使えんのかよ？
（計）そうでもないけど…
What, so if it were yours
you'd know how to use it?
Well, not exactly...
（春哉）ゴチャゴチャ言うな！
残りのバケモンは どこなんだ？
Stop mumbling!
Where's the other one of those monsters?
This thing is only showing
the streets right along the river!
（計）川沿いの道しか
映ってないんだって！
（計）これ ほかの場所
どうやったら見れんだよ？
How do I get it to show me the other areas?
（電子音）
（北条）増えた
There's more now!
（岸本）えっ？
（北条）残りは１匹じゃないのかよ
So there isn't just one?
Maybe that screen's
showing people as dots, too?
（岸本）それ ほかの人たちも
点になって映るんじゃないの？
This is so confusing...
紛らわしいな
But, if that's the case,
it should show Kei and the others, too.
でも だったら
計ちゃんたちも映るはずだ
Can you see the river?
川 映ってない？
Either way I don't think he'd be
walking around on his own.
（加藤）どっちにしても
１人で動くヤツがいるとは思えない
So that must mean this dot is...
だとすると この点は…
Here it comes...
来たぞ
（加藤・岸本）あっ…
（亮太）あっ… 怖いのが また来た
That scary thing is back...
Don't you worry, Ryota, those guys will...
大丈夫だよ
亮太 あのおにいちゃんたちが…
Get out of here! Now!
逃げてくれ 早く！
Go now!
早く行け　あんたたちまで
守りきれるかどうか分からない
There's no guarantee that
we can protect you two!
Go as far as you can!
（加藤）なるべく離れるんだ
（北条）こ… これは…
What the...
あっ…
（加藤）どうした？ あっ…
What's wrong?
も… もう１匹…
Another one!
手で捕まえるぞ
（北条）はぁ？ 何言ってんだ？
We'll get them with our bare hands!
What? Are you crazy?
With guns, if you miss them,
you're out of luck.
銃は外れたらアウトだ
確実な方法で やる
We'll use something
more reliable instead!
You have a point, but still...
そりゃ そうだが…
あっ… ハッ！
（加藤）どうした？
What's wrong?
あっ…
（北条）一体 何匹いるんだ？
How many of them are there?
Yuzo.
（鈴木星人）裕三(ゆうぞう)君？
（加藤）ウワッ！
Kato!
（岸本）加藤君！
This is how you catch them! Pay attention!
こうやって捕まえるんだ
見といてくれ！
There's more?
（北条）また？
This is...
こんな… こんなの…
Kato!
加藤君！
Kishimoto...
（計）岸本 あいつ 撃てねえよ
He can't shoot it.
But... We don't have time for that!
（岸本）でも
そんなこと言ってる場合じゃ…
Hey, do you think that scary robot
will be back again?
（亮太）ねえ また来るかな？
あの怖いロボット
We'll be fine.
（カヨ）大丈夫よ 大丈夫
I'm sure we'll be okay if
we can find somewhere to hide.
どこかに隠れてれば きっと…
You just bring me that frickin'
Suzuki Alien or whatever.
（春哉）なにが鈴木星人だよ？
I'll tear that piece of shit apart!
あんなロボットの出来損ない
俺が ぶっ殺してやるぜ
まだなのかよ？ ああ？
Hey, you found it yet? Well?
There it is...
（計）いた
But...
けど…
（春哉）“けど” 何だ？
But what?
I don't know why but... It's huge.
なんか でかいぜ
（鉄男）ああ？
（春哉）関係ねえってんだ
It doesn't matter!
It's in there.
（計）あそこだ
（春哉）…しゃ 行け
All right. Get movin'.
What, me first?
（計）俺が先かよ？
Of course, ya frickin' moron!
（春哉）当たり前(めえ)だ バカ！
（計）ウッ！
Shit!
くそ！
I could kill him now,
こいつ やったって 残りの
鈴木星人つぶさないと意味ねえしな
but there's no point unless
we kill the rest of Suzuki aliens...
Damn it!
ちくしょう…
My suit...
スーツが…
ンッ… ハァ…
Now his suit's ruined, too.
おしゃかか…
（岸本）加藤君…
Kato!
If you can't shoot them then I will...
加藤君が撃てないなら私が！
Stay back, Kato!
（岸本）加藤君は下がってて！
加藤君は殺させない！
I won't let you kill Kato!
I won't let you kill him!
This is for him! For Kato!
加藤君のためなら！
That's enough! Just run!
もういい！ 逃げてくれ！
（岸本）加藤君こそ逃げて！
Kato, get out of here!
Get out of here quick!
早く逃げろ！
Like this, right?
こうやんのかよ？
（春哉）ここか？
（計）多分
Is this it?
I think so...
Try our
delicious
wings!
Yeah, this is it all right.
間違いねえ
（計）なんか…
There...
There's... so many of them in there.
なんか…
すんげえいる この中に
Hey, Get in there.
おい 入れや
（計）はぁ？
I thought you were gonna tear 'em apart.
（鉄男）てめえが
ぶっ殺すんじゃなかったのかよ？
Shut up!
（春哉）うるせえ！
Now get in there.
お前 入れ
（計）ンッ…
I'll frickin' blow your head off!
（春哉）撃つぞ こら
（亮太）
お… おしっこしたい　おしっこ…
I gotta pee! I gotta pee!
Can't you hold it in?
（カヨ）我慢できないの？
（亮太）おしっこ！ お母さん！
I gotta pee! Mommy!
Then just do it here.
（カヨ）じゃ ここでしなさい
（亮太）ウウッ…
Hey!
（北条）おい
（加藤・岸本）あっ…
What do we do?
どうする？
（加藤）待て
Just wait...
What the hell is wrong with this thing?
（北条）どうしたんだ？ こいつ
Where's the old lady and the kid?
ばあさんと子供は？
（岸本）先に逃げたと思うけど
I think they ran ahead of us.
ヤバイ！ あいつら あの２人を
追ってったんじゃないのか？
Crap...
The other aliens might have
gone after them!
（加藤）行こう
Let's go!
あっ…
おばあちゃん おばあちゃん！
Grandma! Grandma!
Try our
delicious
wings!
Shit... I'm not wearing a suit.
やべえ… スーツ着てねえんだぞ
出てきたら どうすんだよ？
What am I supposed to do if they attack me?
What the hell am I gonna do?
どうすんだよ！
（カヨ）亮太 聞いて
おばあちゃん ここにいるから
Listen to me, Ryota.
I'm going to stay here.
You go on and run out the back.
亮太は後ろから逃げなさい
What about you?
（亮太）おばあちゃんは？
（泣き声）
Grandma will take care of them.
おばあちゃん やっつけちゃうから
（亮太）ヤダよ 恥ずかしいよ
No! This is embarrassing!
（カヨ）走って ほら
（亮太）ウッ…
Go on now. Run!
（亮太）おばあちゃん…
Grandma...
Officer! Help!
おまわりさん！
助けて おばあちゃんが！
My grandma, she's...
（亮太）おばあちゃん…
Grandma!
おばあちゃん おばあちゃん…
お… おばあちゃん…
Grand...
（カヨ）大丈夫 亮太…
Don't worry, Ryota...
There's nothing here.
（計）いない
てめえ ２階 行ってねえだろう？
２階も見てこい
You dumbass, you forgot about upstairs!
Go check up there!
いねえっつってんだろう！
I said there's nothing here!
てめえが
すんげえいるっつったんだろうが
You're the one who told me
there's a bunch of them!
行けよ　行かねえと撃つぞ！
Go!
I'll shoot you if you don't!
It's possible that the machine
could've been broken, right?
あんな端末
壊れてるかもしれねえだろう
い… いねえっつってんだよ
デブ野郎！
I already told him there's
nothing here, that fat fuck!
（鈴木星人）裕三君？ 裕三君？
Yuzo?
Yuzo.
（鈴木星人）裕三君？
裕三君？
Yuzo.
Hajimari wa dare demo junshin muku na baby
Nigai mi kajitte mo kujikecha
dame yo walk straight
Satta koto da kedo ame no naka
zukizuki itamu yo
I'm lonely as floating ice
Yaseta yubi ni kiss o shite
Naita anata o omoidasu yo
Kore de owari da to shite mo
Saigo no kiss wa wasurenai yo
Wasurenai yo
Kare no kiss o wasurenai yo
What is that bird?
（北条）あの鳥 何だよ？
あいつ 連れてかれちゃったじゃん
The guy was taken away.
Huh? Something got shot.
あっ 何か撃ってんじゃん
オッ… 落ちてくんじゃん
バカでえ
It's falling. Stupid...
Next time: "Please Die".
次回 “死んで下ちい”
Is this the end? Eh?
Next time: "Please Die".
“ちい”じゃねえよ “さい”だよ
Is this the end? Eh?
Moron. It's "PLEASE", not "Please".